Okay, now that you know how to add
things, now it's time to learn how to
delete them. So, let's say we want to
remove this off of the screen because
there are duplicates. We don't need two
of the exact same picture here. Um, so
let's talk about how we do that
dynamically. So, what I've done up here
is I've added an on click to this very
first div, and it has a function called
remove me. And if I scroll down to the
bottom, I've created the function called
remove me. And removing is pretty dang
simple. You say document dot query
selector. And I'm just going to remove
the very first div element. So to do
that, I'm going to look for the first
div that has a card attribute. And
because query selector grabs the first
one, I have now grabbed an element. Once
you've grabbed the element you want to
remove, you type dot remove.
And it's that simple. So if you come
over here and you click on it, boom,
we've deleted the card. And now this
card expands to take up the full space
because that's how the CSS was set up.
We have successfully deleted a card. All
that work to learn how to create,
retrieve, and update. And to delete, you
just find it and do remove and you're